Mahdieh Chavoshi

Web3 & Blockchain researcher
Smart Contract Developer & Auditor
SQL Server & C# Web Developer

chavoshi.mahdieh@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mahdieh-chavoshi

github.com/chavoshimahdieh/chavoshimahdieh

2 Iran, Tehran

+98 912 694 9480

Solid understanding of blockchain concepts, Ethereum standards and Solidity programming language as well as experience in using Ethereum's JavaScript SDKs (web3.js, ethers.js), remarkable knowledge of web3 attacks and smart contract intricate security policies, as well as knacking in auditing caused great enthusiasm for the web3 and blockchain and *making decision to jump in to this field of work*.

Web Developer with experience in Implementing business logics using ASP.NET, C#.NET, MS SQL. Skilled in requirements analysis, design, development, maintenance and production support of business applications. Expertized in developing SQL Server databases, optimizing queries and improving database performance. Familiar with Version Control Systems such as Git (Github, Azure Devops).

EXPERIENCE

Infinit8-Landrocker.io (June 2023 - Present)

Smart Contract Developer & Auditor

- -Development and execution of an efficient transparent token distribution mechanism
- -Design and execution of vesting and ICO (Initial Coin Offering) smart contracts.
- -Integration of a concealed reward mechanism using statistical models.
- -Design and execution of marketplace smart contracts to selling off-chain assets (EIP712), NFT1155, and NFT721 assets.
- -Took a leading role in providing architecture review, testing strategy formulation, and auditing smart contracts

Iranian English-language *Press TV* network (Apr 2017 - Present)

C# .Net Web Developer and Programmer

Karestan javan Co. (Jan 2018 - Mar 2019)

SQL Server Developer and Programmer (Generate scripts to convert and transform data from a database to a different one)

IT Organization-Yazd City Hall (Oct 2013 - Apr 2017)

SQL Server Developer and Programmer- C# .Net Web Developer and Programmer

Farazsystempardaz Co. (Mar 2012 - Oct 2013)

C# .Net Web Developer and Programmer

Chargoon Co. (Oct 2011 - Feb 2012)

C# .Net Web Programmer

Chavosh Aryaneh Computer Institute (Feb 2009 - Jul 2010)

Establisher, Manager of Institute and Teacher

Tooska New Way Co. (Dec 2007 - Sep 2011)

C# .Net Web Developer and Programmer

Pinponking Co.(Taiwan) (Apr 2007-Dec 2007 & Apr 2009-Oct 2009)

C# .Net Web Developer and Programmer

Iran Telecommunication Research Center (Jan 2005 - Mar 2007)

C#.Net Web Developer and Programmer, Researcher, Documenter on the Mobile and Core teams in NGN Project

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Computer Networks (2015-2017), *Iran University of Science and Technology(IUST)-GPA 3.85*

Thesis Title

Destructive Attacks Detection and Response System for Physical Devices in Cyber-Physical Systems

Published Paper in

2019 International Conference on Cyber Security and Protection of Digital Services (June 2019, Oxford, UK) https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8884999

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering (2001-2006), University of Kashan-GPA 3.08

Thesis Title

Analysis, design and implementation of E-Office system

SKILLS

- Blockchain technology
- Cryptography
- Consensus algorithm
- Distributed systems
- Zero knowledge proof
- **EIP standards:** EIP721, EIP20, EIP1155, EIP2981, EIP712,EIP1167, EIP2981
- **Development tools:** truffle, hardhat, foundry
- Development languages: Solidity
- Security tools: slither, mythx
- Querying tools: Web3js, Etherjs
- Testing tool: mocha, coverage
- Smart contract design patterns
- Indexing and querying blockchain data: TheGraph

- Maintenance: Git, CI/CD
- DataBase: SQL Server Development &
 - Programming
- Entity Framework Core-Ling
- Object oriented programming
- Development languages: C++, C#, JavaScript,
 TypeScript
- HTML5
- CSS3

STRENGTH

LANGUAGES

- Written and Oral Collaboration	Persian	
- Problem Solving	English	
- Detailed Oriented	Eligiisii	
- Continuous Self Study	French	

2021-02 IELTS Academic – B2
 2013-03 TCF Tout Public – B1

CERTIFICATIONS

2023-12	Decentralized Finance (DeFi) Opportunities and Risks - Duke University
	https://coursera.org/share/d71ffcad3a5e3d9dc4b3cd4f1d41698e
2023-12	Decentralized Finance (DeFi) Deep Dive - Duke University
	https://coursera.org/share/f5cc034afee84b045ef9a7d9f47ed503
2023-03	Bitcoin Infrastructure Course Certificate - BSV Academy
	https://bitcoinsv.academy/student/certificate/15adc2044e61b45cd27d78ed5869434e
2023-03	Bitcoin Theory Course Certificate - BSV Academy
	https://bitcoinsv.academy/student/certificate/e53da0660d5d695870b49aee039f9148
2022-08	Blockchain Basics - University at Buffalo
	https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/2EFP8FTH97GA
2022-08	Blockchain Platforms - University at Buffalo
	https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/8ZYWVVPNAR3Y
2022-08	Decentralized Applications (Dapps) - University at Buffalo
	https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/J9B9AK6KLAG6
2022-08	Smart Contracts - University at Buffalo
	https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/TESVJ69T9A3J